Yeah!
It's Wantats.
I'm Wantats today.
Nice to meet you.
Cute!
So cute!
Thank you very much.
Well, let's get started with the photo shoot, shall we? Please take care of it.
Please take care of them.
Yes, please.
Yay!
Please.
Yes, please.
Meet outside Coach
G guit Assassin
Leisure Lesson
No way Lucifone оказ
experiments
What happened?
Oh, Mr. Clever!
Oh, my God! Thank you!
Mr. Clever!
Thank you!
I'm so happy.
What a dream come true for a kid.
I think we could all be Clever.
Tiny.
Aah!
Good job!
All right. All right.
Cute.
Jude fen Jude fen
亲 Kannan
Kannan
encounter
do
heaven
buddy meio
he
I don't love you One Double Flickr
Yay!
You and me, we're the standard, you and me, you and me, you and me, you and me
Heart in your hand, good friends bond, simpatico cream.
Yes, thank you.
Thank you for your time.
Good morning. - Good morning.
Thank you.
Hey, Popian.
Cute.
What do you look like?
Wow!
Cute.
Let's see.
What do you look like?
Cute.
I used to remember the ending theme to all the Pretty Cure shows I used to watch.
Look.
Here's the making of.
I'm wearing my dog's hair as well! I'm also wearing my dog's haircut as much as he does.
Kokumon
I also got a Kokumon headset!
Please wait for me.
Music
Very cute girl!
Hi!
He's so nice!
What's wrong with you, you little moo goo goo?
What's wrong with you?
Don't just eat.
You have so much energy!
You've got chi. You've got chi.
You need chi.
Stop it, stop it, stop it.
Energy up!
Chilli's all muggy, right?
Your chi is googly, right?
I'm going to run as fast as I can
Smile and
Look at me, look at me
The sparkle in the air
The chi
I carve all the hearts in the world
A bond of friendship is evolving
Collecting the thrill of the moment
One and all
Growing full of color
I'll always be by your side from now on
So much happiness, forever and ever
Evolution ends Evolution Ends
Here
Wait a minute.
You can put it here.
Put it down.
I'm going to put it in the bottom.
That's what they do.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no. It's fate again.
I see... I see...
So I'll put it in and drop it, and I'll make it mine, Hiro.
I'll put it here.
Once you put it back in like this, it means something.
Put it in here.
Maybe it'll come out.
When we're dancing.
It's fate, I guess.
How long?
I don't know.
It's coming down.
I wonder if there's anything here in Hilo.
This is terrible.
This is terrible!
It falls down, and then I put it in, and then I put it back in.
There's no place to put it... for me.
It's right here.
Okay, here... put “score” in there.
Put “score” in there.
I can't find it anymore.
And Hiro's might be the one that fell out.
I don't have Hiro's, and the one that fell out has to be Hiro's, too.
I wasn't the only one.
That's great, it's been waiting for me.
I'm sorry.
I showed you our rescue theater.
I don't get it.
But you're cute. But it's cute.
It was hard to dance like Ebitu has never danced before.
First of all, I think Clicure is cute.
I mean, dancing with the characters from “Clicure”...
Isn't it a dream?
A dream?
I've only seen them on stage and in the audience.
I was with them.
And they were so sweet to me.
He's so cute!
Excuse me, excuse me, excuse me.
Why are you sorry?
I'm sorry.
You can't beat him in the Clicqué.
I did it.
I'm sorry.
But... there's no back-and-forth.
I'm so sorry.
What's the point of all this?
I'm not supposed to show you the middle school theater.
Carry on, carry on, carry on!
He was so cute!
I like him.
Good-looking Mary!
This is quite a sedan, isn't it?
It sure is.
I really like Yuna.
I like it a lot.
I know.
I like her twin-talented look.
So cute!
Twintal awareness.
Twin Tull Consciousness.
I was wondering if I have to stand on my feet with Mr. Pretty Cure.
Yes, I do.
I'm doing twin-tal awareness today. Today we're doing Twin Tull Consciousness.
What is twin-tal awareness?
I'm not doing it with consciousness.
But the fans are doing it with a twin-taru mindset.
I don't always have my decorations on today, but...
I can see that.
Me, too.
I'm sleeping with Mr. Pretty Cure, so...
I'm wearing a rehearsal dress.
And it's a very precious time.
I've been looking at it like this today.
I've seen it so much, it's in my eyes.
And I've been looking at it during the breaks.
I went into the man store.
national sales
This is a video.
He's not there.
This video.
More appeal.
Cute girl.
This is Yuma Sakura.
Nakamura Yuma.
They are all here.
Yuuma is the next one-shot.
Yu no Emma.
One shot.
Are we almost there?
Not a little more.
Oh!
Wow!
Yeah! Yeah!
Yeah! Yes!
Thank you for watching!
ome
me
me ME.
Mr. Scary is a great thing, isn't it?
Sorry, the bread is great. Autocar
Sometimes we all fan out together.
That's normal.
Keep it sporting.
So you can see my face.
But this one's cuter
Love me with you yeah Cute
Plik is a cup of fey marie
Dokoman all together
Fashionable man
this people become a spike or
Oh, yeah, just a step
Cah!
Well then, the A&B singer show
The bag's got a catch.
Loveliness, you know the catch.
Colorful, quirky, totemic.
More than exciting. Sukkoly.
Tockory, colorful, quirky.
Toot-toot, toot-toot. Sukkie, sukkie.
I'm so happy!
I can protect it if it's shiny or not.
Pajamas.
I'm hungry!
Cute stomachs
Meat after each meal
Eat it all, bran!
persistent
phenomenal
Good, good, good
I got a little dirty
Oh, I'm a little dirty.
Okay, I'm going to go now.
Yes, B
That was so cute. She was so cute!
Elena
A Row
Ohhhhhh come on in here for the last time
Thank you Winter.
Thank you all so much.
Thank you.
Oh, oh, oh, oh. Well, let's all look at each other.
Take a come back brother força
Thank you, Father!
menti
I have a pair of pajamas that I don't wear now, but I have them and I wear them every day and I used to sleep in them.
I also had a pair of pajamas that I don't wear anymore, but I had them and I wore them every night and slept with them.
I used to sleep in a dark room with a blanket over my head and tell my mom to watch me.
So I was really excited today.
Thank you for watching.
I'll just be a viewer.
Wait, now that's really cute.
Se-no!
Seino
Fine Sports
He's doing it.
Fine sports!
Wait, no!
He's so cute.
He's posing with his fingers in the middle.
Okay, okay.
That feels good.
Ready?
Let's do it.
Let's go, let's go
Se, se, se
congratulations!
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much
thank you
thank you Thank you.
To the person next to me, like this
Oh, yes, yes.
It's like we can all enjoy it together.
Se-no!
Okay.
Two more.
Two more people...
Oh, I think that's a good idea.
Let's be friends.
Let's do it.
What do we do?
What are you putting in there?
Nice.
So cute!
I wonder where Wonderful went?
Cookie!
He went for a walk.
Good morning.
She's so cute.
What's with the hair?
You'll die next time.
Your hair is cute.
You too.
Cut.
She looks sad.
He's sleeping.
Oh, he's sleeping.
He's fine, isn't he?
Yes, he is.
He's cute.
How is she?
Lovely Creeceen.
Cute!
Pretty Cure
Nippoi Memory
Memory Memory
wrinkle wrinkle
wrinkle
Nippoi Memory
Nippoi memory
Music please.
Thank you very much.
I was the new store owner. Thank you very much.
Yay!
by H.
Thank you for watching